I'm telling you that our goal by the
end of the year is to reach a
billion in revenue, but you can
imagine that when you reach that goal no
one will notice.  Companies
that today make 10 or 100 billion
revino will start saying to themselves,
"But maybe this market makes sense, maybe
we should have our own offering,
we should try to win it."  So on the
one hand, I remain very bullish and
passionate about what we do at
Repit, because we are truly one of the
few companies in the world that thinks
only about this.  While it's true that
Google, Microsoft, Antropic, Open AI,
none of them will stay asleep,
competitive dynamics are very
difficult both to predict and to
navigate.  There may have been companies
that have reached that level of
success and they don't disappear overnight
, but they may go public and
then fail to grow
organically again or are almost
forced into acquisition.  These are all
scenarios that you would not describe as
negative.  What I'm experiencing is an
exceptional story also from a personal point of
view, but to play the role I
have in life you have to be
100% paranoid, so every morning
I wake up and it's not like I say to myself "Ah, how
cool! Beat it".
Exact.  I think, “Ah, what will happen
when Antropic decides to build
a Cloud Code alternative for
knowledge workers?”  And yes, they essentially did it
, they didn't launch cloud
coworking, but on the other hand they
launched their marketplace and we are
one of the six initial partners they
brought into the marketplace.  There are many
companies today that buy both Cloud Code
Replit and serve
completely different users within
the company.